Track 1.2 Unit 1 Grammar Activity 1
Bài 1.2 Đơn vị 1 Ngữ pháp Bài tập 1
Listen and draw lines
Nghe và vẽ đường nối
It's a nice day in the park.
Đó là một ngày đẹp trời trong công viên.
Carlo is eating his lunch.
Carlo đang ăn trưa.
Hugo and Aaron are playing football.
Hugo và Aaron đang chơi bóng đá.
They always play football in the park after school.
Họ luôn chơi bóng đá trong công viên sau giờ học.
Emily is eating an ice cream.
Emily đang ăn kem.
Maria and Juan are doing their homework.
Maria và Juan đang làm bài tập.
They always do their homework on Tuesday.
Họ luôn làm bài tập vào thứ Ba.
Mrs Dobbs is walking in the park.
Bà Dobbs đang đi dạo trong công viên.
She walks in the park every day.
Bà ấy đi dạo trong công viên mỗi ngày.